Abhay Sharma

https://www.linkedin.com/in/abhaysharma10 | abhay.9e@gmail.com | +91 8586000143

Summary

A performance and growth marketer with three years of experience with companies like DECA games, FamPay and Paytm-Nearbuy. Previously, founded two businesses: a marketing agency and a sports e-commerce company, and look forward to working & solving problems in a fast-paced and growth-oriented organisation.

Experience

DECA Games – Berlin, Germany

February 2023 - May 2023

DECA Games is a game publisher and developer of video games

Marketing Specialist, Consultant

- Worked for the organic user acquisition of four popular game titles, each boasting over 100 million installs on the Google Play Store & Apple App Store
- Effectively enhanced the brand visibility of these games, while driving substantial growth in their weekly revenues, while building a playbook for the same.

FamPay - Bangalore, India

January 2021 - January 2023

FamPay is India's first UPI payments app and VISA card for teens

Performance Marketer

- Led new user acquisition, growing from total of 300k installs to 12M+ installs while reducing CAC by 90% over 2 years.
- Grew transacting users from 50k to 2M+, while increasing retention from ~30% to ~75% by developing an LTV based customer acquisition model through data modelling & attribution issues while working on tools such as Google analytics, firebase, appsflyer etc.
- Collaborated with teams from Facebook, Google, Snapchat, Appsflyer, Branch, affiliate & programmatic partners.

Paytm-Nearbuy - Delhi, India

July 2019 - January 2021

India's leading financial services company that offers full-stack B2B & B2C payments & financial solutions

Senior Associate, Business Solutions

- Grew the overall LTV of the acquired user by more than 18% through effective user acquisition and re-activation of churned users, resulting in a direct impact on the bottom line.
- Collaborated with category leaders to introduce a new plan for home storefront merchandising and increased the conversion rate by 25% in 6 months.

Ads with Benefits - Delhi, India

August 2020 - February 2023

Partner

• Grew reach & revenue for brands like Parle-G, Future Generali, Fevicol and more to help them engage with the marketing community which yielded a revenue of INR 5,00,000 for the company.

Dream Out Loud Media - Gurgaon, India

May 2014 - April 2018

Co-Founder

- Founded a marketing firm housing brands like Jio, Hike, UC Browser etc and generated a revenue of INR 50 lacs.
- Launched a sports e-commerce platform to plan & execute marketing and operations strategies to generate a revenue of INR 10 lacs.

Education

GrowthX, India April 2022 – May 2022

Worked with the top 1% growth leaders in India to solve the biggest real life growth problems.

Stoa School, India May 2021 – Dec 2021

General Management Program

A.P.J Abdul Kalam Technical University (formerly UPTU)

Aug 2015 - July 2020

Bachelor of Technology – Electronics & Communication

Additional

Advisor to Mr. Ankur Warikoo for his personal brand and helped reach 1.5 million followers